# Artur Kondas

#### Contact

Personal Site: akondas.com

Email: arturkondas@gmail.com

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/arturkondas

### **Profile**

A Software Engineer generalist with over three years of experience spanning from IT Support to teaching and Software Development. Using Belbin's Team Roles, best described as a combination of Plant and Monitor Evaluator; I'm always full of ideas and unconventional approach to problems, but still being able to see all the options and judge accurately. Willing to learn and improve, but at the same time to teach and help others.

### Skills

Programming Languages Go (Golang, very much preferred), Javascript, C/C#, Python, Ruby

Database PostgreSQL, MongoDB, MySQL dGraph, Neo4J

Frameworks/Libraries gRPC, React, Vue, Mocha, Chai, Jasmine, ffmpeg

Cloud & Orchestration AWS, GCP, Kubernetes, RDS, EC2, S3, Docker

CI/CD Jenkins, Puppet

Version Control Git, GitHub, GitLab, BitBucket

Project/Team Management Agile, Scrum, ITIL

# **Employment**

ECS Digital / Go Software Engineer

July 2019 - Present

- Building state-of-the-art, microservices-based, bespoke tools using Go, including AI
- Data analysis using Python
- Event-Driven architecture with Kubernetes API
- Database design, maintenance and management
- Custom CLIs built with Go
- Consulting other teams on Go projects
- Code refactoring
- Delivering internal training

Calipsa / Full Stack Software Engineer

January 2019 - July 2019

- NodeJS / Vue Software Engineer
- Building backend applications for video scraping, conversion and AI-ready implementation
- Implementing architecture changes
- DB management and maintenance

### / Scrum Master

March 2019 - July 2019

- Project and team-workload management
- Implemented and lead Agile ceremonies

## Sparta Global / Software Development Technical Trainer

September 2018 - January 2019

- Full Stack, DevOps and Testing trainer
- Teaching modern JavaScript (ES6/ES8), React, Ruby/Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL, ISTQB testing principles, DevOps and Agile methodologies
- Team/Tech Lead, Product Owner, Scrum Master
- Writing curriculum, lessons and labs for the students
- Received praise from the board for tacking unexpected challenges and helping the company

### Freelance / Full-Stack Developer

January 2017 - June 2018

- Designing, building and maintaining Full-Stack apps and APIs
- Working with JavaScript, HTML5/CSS3, React, Vue, Angular 2

# ABB / Application Specialist

January 2018 - June 2018

- Level 3 Application Specialist
- CMS, MSSQL and JavaScript code mainenance
- HTML/CSS, XML parsing
- Documentation maintenance
- Release automation and checks

#### / IT Support Specialist

March 2017 - December 2017

- Level 2 Support Specialist
- Incident management, coordination with response teams, bug fixing
- DB maintenance, XML/JSON debugging

### Capgemini / English Customer Service Advisor

August 2016 - February 2017

- First line technical support
- KPI/SLA management
- OOH Incident management

#### Education

# Cracow University of Technology Power Engineering / BE

2013 - 2017

Engineering thesis: Acoustic measurements of electrical engines

# Languages

- Polish (Native)
- English (Fluent)
- Spanish (Basic)

# Certfications

- .NET advanced Comarch June 2018
- Excel Intermediate Langolian November 2017
- ITIL Foundation Conlea June 2017
- Oracle SQL Introduction Langolian April 2017
- AutoCAD 2015 Intermediate Cadsoft June 2015

# Open Source / Volunteer

- Speaker Devops Playground
  - Delivered a live-stream workshop on building a ready-to-deploy, CRUD API in Go. Link here
- Guest Speaker ColorInTech
  - Delivered two workshops on annual ColorInTech events
- Contributor Grafana Labs
  - Contributed to 7.0.0 beta #22898
- Contributor Rod
  - Contributing to overall functionality of a Chrome Devtools driver in Go
- Contributor / Translator GitHub
  - Translated Unshaky and Rectangle to Polish
- Translator Microsoft
  - Contributed to VS Code translation to Polish
- Technical Trainer Codebar
- Technical Trainer CodeFirst: Girls
  - Delivered two editions of CF:G

### References

References available on request

# Disclaimer

Please contact prior to phone call, I am not picking up unsolicited calls.

I hereby give consent for my personal data included in my offer to be processed for the purposes of recruitment in accordance with the Data Protection Act as of 29 August 1997 (Journal of Acts of 2002, No 101, pos. 926 with later amendments)